There's one way to cure Gut-Breaking Grass.
What's the cure?
A life for a life.
That's right.
To save this friend of yours,
it takes a life for a life.
My brother stayed silent to help you.
But since you're so insistent,
he can help you trade your life for your friend's now.
Great!
Old Qian can be saved!
Old Qian!
You're going to be saved!
I'll save you, I'll save you.
I'll trade my life for yours.
Doctor, save me, doctor!
Save me!
You trade your life for his!
Why should my brother's life pay for his?
She's asking why.
I'll tell you why.
Because your brother is a doctor.
Because of A healer's compassion.
If he doesn't save him, who will?
Doctors heal and save lives, right?
Exactly!
So saving lives is only natural.
You...
Ren Feifan.
You may refuse to save Old Qian today,
but Premier Medical Hall's signboard,
I will definitely
tear it down.
How dare you!
Young Master Wang.
Do you still remember me?
I'm also a doctor of Premier Medical Hall.
Him — I'll save him.
Don't you dare touch our signboard.
Young Master, seal his meridians first.
Otherwise, I couldn't save him even if I died twice.
Young Master.
Follow me.
Check my pulse.
This is...
a Fatal Pulse.
Young Master.
I don't have much time left.
If I can save Premier Medical Hall's name before I go,
I'll die without regrets.
Master Zhang.
The toxins in your body
came from years of preparing herbs.
I can find a way.
Though I can't cure it completely,
I can prolong your life as much as possible.
Besides,
Today's incident is a trap set by Wang Wenhao.
I can shut Premier Medical Hall down.
I can even take the signboard down.
But your life,
I will definitely save it.
My days are numbered.
Living is suffering.
Dying
would be a release.
Your father recognized my worth.
I've worked half my life with a true friend,
I'm already content.
If you save my life today,
we'll lose not just Premier Medical Hall's signboard,
but also our ancestors' teachings.
You
can afford that loss,
but I cannot!
True, this is Wang Wenhao's trap.
But if you don't save him today,
you'll be shutting out everyone outside
who believes in us.
Can you do that?
I...
Young Master, become a great healer!
To shelter all humanity,
to save the common folk!
Go prepare.
Even if you don't save him today,
I'll die beneath this plaque anyway.
Die to prove my resolve.
Feifan is humbled by your lesson.
At this moment,
what I can't let go of most
is my little granddaughter.
After I'm gone,
Young Master,
will you shelter her, protect her, and teach her?
Everyone.
This is Zhang Cheng, our doctor at Premier Medical Hall.
Doctor Zhang is willing to sacrifice himself today to save this patient.
So with all of you as witnesses,
watch how I save this patient.
I hope after this,
you'll all trust Premier Medical Hall from now on.
This, this...
A healer's compassion!
Truly A healer's compassion!
A man of great righteousness!
A life for a life!
Indeed.
Thank you, Mr. Wang, for this generous gift.
Feifan will repay you handsomely one day.
He's truly a miracle healer!
He actually saved him!
He truly traded his own life to save another.
Thank you for saving my friend.
Yueyue.
Grandpa, you're awake.
Where am I?
I'm not dead?
Master Zhang.
You're safe now.
I brought you home.
Gut-Breaking Grass, aside from a life for a life,
has no antidote.
Here's the thing, Master Zhang.
The poisoned patient
had very little toxin in his body,
and the poisoning was mild.
I'm guessing
he took the Gut-Breaking Grass just before entering Premier Medical Hall.
Then he spat some out when Wang Wenhao wasn't looking.
His chest and cuffs both reeked of Gut-Breaking Grass.
Everyone fears death.
Of course,
there are exceptions.
Except for you.
A man of great righteousness.
You little brat, you dare joke with me now.
Though no life needed to be traded,
then why did I pass out earlier?
Wang Wenhao used despicable tactics.
To force his man to take the poison,
he must have threatened his family.
If Wang realized he spat out the poison,
it would endanger his entire family.
So I just let Wang Wenhao think he'd gained the upper hand.
That makes sense.
Then you and Yue'er should rest at home for now.
Don't go outside.
Wait until I've dealt with the Wang family completely.
That day will come soon.
I'll draw the poison out for you.
Ruo Jin.
You went to see that Ren Feifan again.
Last time you came back covered in injuries,
and they still haven't healed.
You're the one who put him behind bars.
And you're the one who insisted on keeping the baby.
Think about it.
Will he forgive you because of this child?
Whether he forgives me or not,
it won't change the fact that I love him.
You...
Mom.
Don't call me that.
I just can't see what's so great about Ren Feifan.
His background and family are nothing compared to yours.
He's only with you to marry up into our family.
You're already engaged to Wang Wenhao.
Wang Wenhao is the sole heir of the Wang family.
He'll inherit the entire Wang Group one day.
Daughter, use your head and think it through.
Wenhao.
Yes, yes.
No problem.
Wenhao's invited you over for dinner.
Get yourself ready.
Dress up nicely.
Don't upset his family again.
Think about that child of yours.